One second, please.
One second. Can't see you.
Congratulations, Aarav!
You've topped your university!
Thank you, Chandni. How are you?
I'm good.
This calls for a celebration!
When are you coming to India?
Next week. I'm arriving a little earlier
for the alumni meeting.
I was supposed to be attending too.
But... stupid office work.
- I'm travelling next week.
- Okay.
Try and come, if you can.
Everyone's coming. Chinna, Sameer...
You'll enjoy it.
I read about it on the college group.
But it's not possible.
I understand.
Anyway... see you soon.
- You take care.
- Bye.
Bye.
We were 21 when we first met.
If only we had met now,
things would've been different.
Our lack of maturity got
in the way then.
Our destination seemed to
slip further away.
Chandni is no longer a part
of my life.
But she'll always be
in my heart.
Chand, my heart
Hi, guys. Aarav Rawat.
Mechanical Engineering.
Batch of 2021.
Aarav Rawat!
Oi Hyderabadi biryani!
- How are you, bro?
- All good!
I swear, bro! Why are you so excited?
We video-called only last week.
- But it's four years since we met.
- Forget him. Give me a hug!
- How are you?
- I'm good.
You killed it in the US.
But no American accent?
No accent. No beard either.
- All well?
- Yeah!
What can I say?
I'm just the same.
Nothing's changed, same to same.
And our Mechanical Department?
Four girls back then,
four girls now.
It's still the graveyard
it always was.
Come on! The programme's starting.
We won't get good seats.
Settle down, please.
Thank you very much Settle down.
I've been preparing this speech
for a week.
Here's the bore.
To see former and new students...
it's always very heartening.
It feels very warm and fuzzy inside.
It's guaranteed we'll have
100 percent placements,
and my job as principal is secure!
I'm very proud to be the principal
of this college.
We make good engineers here,
but more importantly,
life-long friendships get made here.
Guaranteed, lifelong friendships.
I hope you all have
a memorable evening.
Have a great time!
Taking the stage now is
a first-year computer science student,
Chandni Prasad.
Let's give her a warm round of applause.
Is it a freshers' or
a cultural programme?
Whatever it maybe,
let's get out of here.
Not bad, bro.
What's got into him?
No one looks as lovely
as you seem to me
We're like those legendary
lovers of old
Sam!
Move!
We're like those legendary
lovers of old
I see you with my eyes closed
Now my eyes no longer
need to dream
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
You look like brother and sister.
Are you mad? They're twinning!
I care far less for myself
Than I care about you
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
No one looks as lovely
as you seem to me
We're like those legendary
lovers of old
No one looks as lovely
as you seem to me
We're like those legendary
lovers of old
Bro, if you're brave enough
to wear this,
forget Chandni, I'd happily
be your girlfriend!
You have to be crazy
when you fall in love.
We're like those legendary
lovers of old
Without you
What's life?
Through your eyes, when
I see myself
I look more beautiful
I have no need to adorn myself
Chandni, wear this.
There's no way he can match the colour.
What do I need now?
Every day is a celebration
when you take me in your arms
It matters little if it's really
a day for celebration
I care far less for myself
Than I care about you
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
No one looks as lovely
as you seem to me
We're like those legendary lovers of old
No one looks as lovely
as you seem to me
We're like those legendary
lovers of old
Without you
What's life?
Chandni, do you realise we've lost
the match?
I know. We'll win the next time.
How?
You were distracted throughout
the match.
Thinking about Aarav?
A little.
He couldn't take his eyes off her.
And she didn't look even once at you.
He's just a regular guy.
That's why I like him.
- What?
- He may be a regular guy,
but he makes me feel so special.
He looks like a soft kind of romantic.
An intense lover.
Are you serious, Chandni?
You've never even spoken to each other.
You think he'd take the initiative?
Aren't you being a bit impulsive,
Chandni?
How to explain?
Whenever I see him, I feel the world
turns more beautiful.
Forget the world! I think you've turned
from engineer to poetess!
You never 'give up' in your studies.
So why give up on anything else?
I'm struggling with Mathematics 2.
Will you help me?
What happened?
So, derivative of a point function
in a particular direction is called...
Directional derivative
along the direction.
You know more than I do.
How can I teach you?
Coffee?
Milk?
Black.
No, there's milk.
What's yours?
I have you in my arms
But I can't get enough of you
Never before have I loved someone
So fully, so deeply
Distance will be unbearable now
Let nothing separate us today
You and me feel like one
How do I find the words...
to express my love?
I can belong to no one else.
Now that you are mine
How do I find the words...
to express my love?
I can belong to no one else.
Now that you are mine
You and me feel like one
- What is it?
- Low attendance.
My backup cigarettes.
If I get stressed, I smoke
three ciggies, back-to-back.
Stress turns to smoke.
Calmness!
Come on! The sun's rising!
Hurry.
Come on.
You okay?
How many do you smoke a day?
One packet maybe. Why?
Smoke that much and I'll get
a throat infection.
Nothing else matters to me
but loving you
You know it's true
youth is the time for love
How do I find the words...
to express my love?
I can belong to no one else
Now that you are mine
How do I find the words...
Our story is on the lips
of the world
How love possesses us
How you and I
Care so little for the world
I wish all these companies came
to our college.
Once I graduate, I'm heading
straight to the US to do my MS.
I'm staying here.
If I go to the US, Mama will be
all alone.
Actually, Indian colleges offer
solid MS degrees.
It's good here too.
Stop the bike!
Our story is on the lips
of the world
How love possesses us
I hope you don't have feelings
for me?
I... no... I...
But I have feelings for you.
to express my love?
Oh, hello! What's going on?
He was flirting in the middle
of the street,
without any bike documents.
He's a good boy, sir.
He's like a brother.
- I'll explain things to him.
- Not to him.
Tell his parents. Give me their number.
Sir, they're students. If you call
their parents, they'll get into trouble.
Those welders were making a racket
since dawn, ruined my mood.
These great lovers of today,
I'll throw them both in jail.
Sir, he made a mistake,
he won't do it again.
Don't talk too much.
Are you stressed?
I am having fun.
And you can't smoke your stress off here.
I quit smoking.
What?
My smoke was irritating
someone's throat.
So I thought I'd stop.
Meaning? You quit?
- You quit?
- Yes.
Forever!
What is it, Chand?
It's all new to me.
No one has sacrificed anything
for my sake.
But I was sacrificed.
My parents didn't get along.
How could they?
My father was violent towards
my mother.
He'd lock me up in a room,
and hit her.
- I told you we were impossible.
- You always say no to everything.
What's your problem?
Everything's an issue.
- Me? I'm making an issue?
- Don't shout.
I could only hear sounds.
Things breaking, mother screaming.
At first I was terrified, then I got
used to it.
Then one day he got up and left.
You know, Aarav,
I was all alone raising myself.
I didn't know what a home was.
I'm sorry you had to endure all this.
No one raised their hand in my home,
but never held hands either.
They stay together,
because that's the done thing.
Our family looks like the ideal family
from the outside.
I have a home,
but it never felt like home.
How did you learn to be so good
to others?
I don't know about the others,
but I love being good to you.
If I see you even once,
- it feels like...
- The world is more beautiful.
Our story is on the lips
of the world
Aarav, Chandni can't go
to the movies today.
Chand, what's wrong?
You okay?
I missed my period.
Oh!
Really?
But, Chand, don't girls sometimes
miss their period?
- It's normal.
- It's been forty days.
And you're telling me now?
Sorry.
Relax, I'll get a pregnancy kit.
We'll check.
Aaru.
An abortion wouldn't create other
health complications, would it?
Shouldn't do. I checked on the Net.
The Net? What, again?
So, should I ask my mother or yours
for advice?
Shh!
Chand, why are you shouting?
You have an app, you could've checked
the app.
So it's my fault?
When did I say it's your fault?
All I meant was...
Did I say it was your fault?
I don't know what I should say.
I'm scared, Chand. Shit scared.
Me too.
Have you decided?
Chandni,
I'll give you two pills.
Take one now, the other
in 48 hours.
The first pill will terminate
your pregnancy.
The second pill will empty the uterus.
All right?
You may bleed a little,
feel nauseous or vomit,
that's not unusual, so don't worry.
Chand!
What happened?
Sorry. I can't do it.
Chand, we'll work it out.
There's a hospital near the college,
why did you come so far?
You crazy?
She hasn't got a virus.
She's pregnant.
She needed to come this far.
Aarav, don't stress. Jyotsna
is talking to her.
Has she gone crazy?
Calm down!
Why are you getting angry?
Why are you doing this, Chand?
We're undergrads.
Our GRE is coming up and, later,
the MS degree.
Our lives are just starting,
and you want to raise a child?
Tell me how.
On the way to the hospital,
I was sure about the abortion.
But while I was waiting,
I felt something.
What are you talking about?
You can't be serious.
You're educated.
You shouldn't say such foolish things.
Chand!
Chandni, listen to me.
Please wait!
- That's not what I meant.
- It's okay. I am foolish.
But you aren't being sensible.
- Jyotsna, Sameer and Chinna would agree.
- They can say what they want.
It's not their lives. It's my life
and my decision.
It's not just your life,
it's my life too.
Aarav, I don't know if it's possible
for such things to happen.
But I felt something inside me.
How can I explain?
I felt a deep connection.
Like I've never felt before.
Chand, think it over.
It's not too late. There's time.
I'm not having an abortion,
of that I'm sure.
Please understand.
Chandni!
Chandni.
It's okay, Aarav.
I'm not asking you
to be responsible.
It's my decision, so it's
my responsibility alone.
Mama will be angry at first,
but she'll accept it.
I mean, I'm all she's got.
I'll have to take a break from studies,
but that's okay.
Many take time off.
When the baby is older,
I can start studying again.
I'll work hard, get a good job,
so I can afford a nanny.
We'll be fine. Sorted!
Is this what you want?
Baby, Mummy, nanny.
You've worked out the whole future?
What about me?
Is there any place for me
in this future of yours?
Can you live without me?
Because I can't live without you.
A future without you?
I don't want it.
Will you marry me?
Chand. My heart
Come closer, closer. Closer.
Now chin down, chin down.
- Okay.
- Yes, now smile!
- Aarav?
- Aarav!
What a nice surprise!
You said he forgot to call.
See? He came in person.
Happy anniversary to you both!
- Thank you!
- Thank you for coming, son.
Who is she?
Mummy, she's Chandni,
my batchmate. Come.
Hello, Chandni.
- Namaste, aunty.
- Namaste, namaste.
- Happy anniversary, aunty.
- Thank you.
Wish me too! My life was ruined, too!
- Happy anniversary, uncle.
- Thank you.
- Sis?
- Why weren't you taking my calls?
Something was wrong with
the network, sis.
The network? Or were you busy
with someone?
Let's get the photo done.
Come.
Closer, please.
Come!
Now smile.
- That's fine.
- Yes.
Say 'cheese'!
She didn't get pregnant by herself.
Very good. Now try explaining
that to Papa.
He went off to become an engineer,
and came back a father!
And Aarav...
Aarav is going to be a father
and she's the mummy!
He went off to become an engineer,
and came back a father!
I had no idea my parents would
react like that.
I'm so very sorry, Chand.
I don't know how Mama will react.
I'm sorry, Mama.
It's okay, my dear, it's okay.
At least you had enough sense
to come to me.
The mistake is made.
It doesn't mean making another
mistake to undo the first one.
Rest today, we'll go to
the hospital tomorrow.
I'll speak to Dr. Gupta.
I'll talk to him. I'll handle everything,
don't worry.
Mama, I've decided I don't
want to have an abortion.
Chandni, please be practical.
You have your whole life ahead
of you.
A child? At your age?
Being a mother is not
some part-time hobby.
It's a fulltime job!
I was your age when I had you,
don't make the same mistake.
I know.
If I hadn't been born, you'd have
been a successful dancer, right?
Chandni, that's not what I meant.
You know this.
So what do you mean?
I did everything for you.
Did you want for anything?
- Education...
- Love.
Didn't you love me less?
I'm a single parent.
I loved you as much as I could.
Didn't you realise I had to make do
with just one parent?
I only got half the love.
That too was so little.
I want this child, Mama.
And I know I'll give it
all the love I never had.
I understand why,
because you were alone, raising me.
But Aarav is with me.
You're sure about this?
Yes.
This has never happened before,
in the history of Hy-Tech.
This is an issue for the College Trustees
and faculty members.
Sir, please. Our careers are at stake.
Don't worry.
Their objections cannot be above
our Constitution.
You both are adults.
You're legally eligible to
get married.
But,
you cannot stay together
in the hostel.
Other students' parents
might object.
It's okay, sir. We'll find a place
off campus.
Good.
If anyone bothers you on campus,
come to me.
Look, you're both brilliant students,
so focus on your studies.
Everything will be okay.
Okay?
- Thank you, sir.
You should thank your batchmates.
They've flooded my office
with cards and flowers!
Now go! Make me proud.
- Thank you, sir.
The family may not be ready,
but the wedding procession is here!
We're tossing a coin to see
who can do the rituals.
Bro, ask the principal
if he will?
Our boy is getting married.
Come one, come all!
You are the star that lights
the dark night
O moon of my heart
You are the star that lights
the dark night
O moon of my heart
I was given this life of mine
So I'd spend it wanting you
But one lifetime is not enough
To love you
In this lifetime I promise you
That all my lifetimes will belong
to you
O moon of my heart
How do I look?
Like you're mine.
Found that earring you lost?
You stole it! Give it...
Why should I give it back?
With this, I keep one of your ears.
If you mess me around,
I'll pull your ear!
Like this?
Chand! What are you doing?
We're in a temple,
behave yourself.
A love that never fades
It's a love you can test
O moon of my heart
Sir, thanks to his coaching
we passed.
I guaranteed it.
All the students from your
institute will top their exams.
I promise!
Hey, bro!
Why so sad?
You've got the job.
It's only enough to cover monthly bills.
Who's going to pay the rent?
I must find more work.
Bro, when will you study?
Listen. My uncle has a place
near the college.
You can rent it.
No stress, bro. Chinna is here!
Well? Get it?
This great love I feel for you
Has anyone ever seen before?
It is only very rarely
That such a lover is born
I bowed before God
To pray that I win you
Let the Lord above
bless my decision
To love you forever
My heart is now all yours
Your love is like bright moonlight
O moon of my heart
A love that never fades
It's a love you can test
O moon of my heart
Congratulations, Chandni!
You're hired!
Thank you, sir. Thank you, ma'am.
Now open your page 239.
The hammer and the feather story.
Since it is given that F of 1
is less than 8,
we reject 10 and conclude
that F of 1 = 2.
Is that clear? Any doubts?
I have you in my arms
But I can't get enough of you
Bro, why didn't you pick up?
I was teaching.
The phone was on silent.
Jyotsna!
Chand!
I'm so sorry.
My phone was on silent.
Remember, it's the 9th month!
You left it on silent?
- I'm so sorry, Chand.
- Sir, wait here.
Chill, bro. It'll be fine.
Have you chosen a name
for the baby?
Chandni made a list.
But we haven't decided yet.
The baby's father is wanted inside.
How's the progress?
The patient's vital signs are stable.
She's fully dilated.
Okay.
Start pushing, Chandni.
Very good. Start pushing.
Very good.
Well done, good.
Push harder. Push harder.
Try one more time.
Push harder.
Stop!
Chand, relax.
It's okay take a deep breath.
Chandni, take a deep breath.
Very good. Once again.
One...
Relax.
Chandni!
- Chandni, you can't sleep.
- Chandni.
Open your eyes.
The baby's heartbeat is slowing down.
Okay. Try one more time.
Last time, okay?
We'll do it. Last time.
Try once again. Harder!
Last time okay.
We'll do it. Last time.
Try once again. Harder!
Done. Done.
Kavya!
No, no, no.
- Don't be scared.
- She's so tiny.
If she was any bigger,
I'd be dead!
I can't...
Mind her neck.
Ma'am, it's time to feed the baby.
- Sir, can you wait outside?
- Yes.
No, he will stay here.
Okay.
Ma'am, we need to lower the pillow.
Get comfortable.
The baby's nose needs to touch
your nipple.
Yes, that's right.
Congratulations! You're hired.
Thank you, ma'am. Thank you, sir.
We're opening a new unit
in Gurgaon.
It's only a small unit, but it comes
with a lot of responsibility.
Oh, thank you.
If it's at all possible,
may I ask
to join your unit here in Hyderabad?
Is that possible?
It'll be difficult for me,
working away from here.
- Why?
- Actually, my family is here.
Tell your parents this is a great
opportunity for you.
It concerns your future.
Not my parents, sir.
My wife and daughter.
What! Already?
Don't you know child marriage
is a crime in our country?
Look, Aarav, the vacancy
is in our Gurgaon plant.
The choice is yours.
4x + 4 = 1. Answer is...?
Hi, Kavya.
- Chandni, you okay?
- I'm fine.
I don't know why I suddenly
feel like crying, but I'm okay.
Kavya!
It's a given that the inverse
of A is...
I doubt he slept last night.
Yes, sir, please try...
Some unpaid overtime is due.
Okay, sir.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Tell me, Aaru.
The salary from the coaching centre
will be late.
And the rent is due soon.
Shall I take on some private tuition?
Don't worry about it,
just take care of yourself
and Kavya.
I'll handle the rest. Okay?
Go now. You'll be late for class.
Bye.
Chandni, come back for Kavya's shot
in two months.
You all right?
This looks really good on you.
I love it, you know.
- I don't understand a word.
- I'll tell you.
Didn't sir say that last week?
Chand...
Even I got that.
Aaru, can you look after Kavya, please?
I'm studying! I have exams too.
You go to her.
There are four kinds of forces.
Stop, my dear.
What happened to Kavya?
What happened?
- Honestly speaking, the way he spoke...
- It happens.
He really cares.
The rent, Kayva's expenses,
he's handling it all.
He's stressed and he hasn't got
a proper job yet.
That's creating stress
and anxiety.
No, absolutely not.
It concerns your future.
I agree with what he's saying.
There's a minu... ite,
minute...
This is what creates a society
full of stress and anxiety.
Yeah, but responsibility doesn't
come with that.
It's not only...
I have a feeling the women here
agree with me.
Chinna.
Thank God!
I invite you all.
Chinna, we need more than biryani!
One second, guys, sorry,
sorry, just a second.
Hurry! The placement list is up!
This was the last decent company.
That was the last solid company.
It's now out of our reach now.
A new IT startup is coming tomorrow.
Shall we try?
Only a loser would apply to
that company.
Congratulations, Aarav! You're hired!
Thank you, sir.
Congratulations!
Congratulations, Aaru.
How's the biryani?
Sameer, come on.
Leave the plate.
The sun's going down
Your guy's all set
He's got swagger and energy
on the rise
Just look at this beauty
This wannabe Kareena
Her dancing is giving everyone
a high fever
A little hard
A little gentle
A little sentimental
A little mental
Everyone, everyone...
You okay, Aaru?
Aaru? You all right?
I know you aren't happy with your job.
So why did you throw that party?
Aaru, it's your first job.
It doesn't mean this has
to define your career.
All empty talk.
It's easy for you to talk
because you have a good job.
With a good package.
So it's about that?
Am I wrong?
You know my salary package?
What's the difference?
We'll manage.
It makes a difference to me.
I taught Sameer and Chinna,
and they've got good jobs.
Their grades were lousy.
I studied Mechanical Engineering,
and I'm working in an IT startup.
And you want to celebrate it?
I just thought you were worried.
- I'm so grateful to you! Thank you.
- Aarav, please.
Kavya is sleeping.
Let's talk tomorrow. You're tired.
I am tired.
Tired of pleasing you.
Pleasing me?
Meaning?
Meaning...
I'm suffocating, Chandni.
I sacrificed everything for
our relationship.
I ruined my grades,
ruined my placement,
I ruined everything.
Ever asked yourselves,
when you were all preparing
for your exams or job interviews,
what was I doing then?
I was teaching
at the coaching institute.
Why?
So I could take care of Kavya.
Pay the rent.
Do you have any idea
what I've been through?
Physically, mentally, emotionally?
But unlike you, I don't brag.
- I said I'd manage things. Right?
- Sure you did!
I didn't realise your decision
would ruin my career and life.
All I wanted was to be with you,
I loved you.
I didn't want to get trapped
into raising a child.
You're just like your mother.
What did she say?
This girl has trapped our son.
Right?
Don't drag my family into this.
So? If you didn't want all this,
why did you do it?
Because I know how to be responsible.
I'm a responsible man.
So you wanted to be responsible?
You wanted to be a man!
So all the responsibility terrified you?
- You're a child, Aarav. It's beyond you.
- Just shut up!
Sorry.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Sorry, Chandni.
Listen to me.
Chand, listen to me. Chand.
I made a terrible mistake.
I take it back. Sorry, sorry.
Chandni, please...
Open the door. I made a mistake.
Sorry!
Chandni, sorry. I made a mistake.
Open the door.
Chandni, please open the door.
I'll never do it again. Please!
Chandni, just hear me out.
Don't!
You are the star that brightens
the dark night
O moon of my heart
A love that never fades
A love that you can test
Aarav, it was your fault.
If you weren't my brother, I might not
be able to forgive you.
I made a mistake, sis.
I know.
She's right to punish me.
And I'm ready to face it.
Try explaining that to her.
I tried very hard,
but she blocked me from everywhere.
I don't want to lose Kavya
and Chandni...
Convince her you made a mistake,
but you're not a bad person.
Thank you for coming, Chand.
Can I talk to you for two minutes?
How is Kavya?
She's fine. She's at the creche.
And you?
Aarav, I have an important meeting
in half an hour.
I have to feed Kavya.
I'm so ashamed of my behaviour.
I've lost all my self-respect.
I made a terrible mistake
and I'm genuinely very sorry.
Give me a chance, I'll make it up
to you.
I know, Aarav.
I've thought a lot about
that night
and realised the mistake was mine.
I should have refused
to marry you.
You aren't ready to take on
any responsibility.
Not true. I am ready
to take responsibility.
It was a moment's weakness.
It was the job that made me angry.
- One more chance...
- Please don't embarrass me.
My co-workers can see us.
Chandni, I know I messed up badly,
but don't keep me away
from you or Kavya.
I feel so alone without you both.
Please.
I'll text you my address.
You can see Kavya at weekends.
But I will not withdraw
the divorce notice.
Chandni, didn't Aarav just come
to see you?
He messaged me.
Chandni, think carefully.
You love him too.
But my self-respect is more important
than love.
What's wrong?
Hasn't the meeting started?
It got cancelled.
Why?
You know how the US team is, Chandni.
They've sent a mail to HR.
Says, dear Chandni, just look
at your face.
Kevin, I was just terrified.
It wasn't cancelled, I pushed the meeting
by half an hour.
Thank you.
I knew you'd need time.
Differentiate and show me
two values of X.
- In other words...
- These words will do, sir!
So who can tell me the value of X?
Come on, guys, find the value of 'X'.
My Ex was my life!
What's your name?
Did I hurt you, sir?
Are you filing a complaint?
I've been dealing with an ugly
separation for the past few months.
We'll be divorcing soon.
I don't feel anything anymore,
so I have no feelings you can hurt.
If you want to learn,
then tell me the value of X,
if you don't want to learn,
then get the hell out of my class!
Chandni?
Sorry, I think I've come
to the wrong place.
Not at all. This is Chandni's place.
Please come in.
Come, come.
Chandni!
Any problem finding the house?
Please.
Can I get you something to drink?
No. Thank you.
Hi!
Aarav, this is Kevin.
My colleague. He lives next door.
He's been kind enough to rent
this place out to us.
I am both cook and landlord!
I am both Chandni's husband,
and Kavya's Papa.
I know!
I'll get Kavya.
- Look, Kavya.
- Hey, kiddo!
- Paapu is here!
- Hi yes.
Hey, Kavya!
- Kavya!
- Kavya, look.
What is it, Kavya?
Her favourite toy.
- Hi Kavya.
- Kavya.
I'll put her to bed.
It's nothing... she gets upset
seeing new people.
She doesn't see you often enough.
She'll be okay. Why don't you sit?
I'll get you something to eat.
Sorry.
Can you come tomorrow?
She hasn't seen you for a while, so...
So she got a bit upset.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Look, Kavya.
Papa made this just for you.
Here, Kavya...
One more, please.
Look.
Done.
Thank you.
Wow!
My baby.
Let's go.
Papa and Kavya are off together!
Yes.
Guess where to?
To Mama and Papa's college!
Okay.
Aarav, please don't forget
to give Kavya her meds.
Thank you.
My sweetie, come!
Stop now, that's enough.
What's wrong? Why is she crying?
Did you remember her meds?
I left the medicine bag on the train,
by accident.
Meaning she hasn't had her meds?
Why didn't you call me, Aarav?
- I ran after the train...
- Her fever only came down two days ago.
The doctor said she mustn't miss
her antibiotics.
I'll go buy the medicine.
There's no need! I'll do it.
But next time, please don't come.
Don't come?
Meaning what?
What? 'Don't come?'
Meaning I don't want you
to see Kavya.
You don't want... meaning?
No, I don't understand.
Kavya is my daughter.
Why can't I see her?
Chandni, wait!
I admit I made a mistake.
That doesn't mean...
How many more mistakes, Aarav?
I apologised for my mistake.
I apologise and I'll keep apologising.
And what did you do? You sent me
a divorce notice.
Such harsh punishment
for one mistake.
It's not about one mistake.
I realised that day,
Kavya and our marriage...
was also your mistake.
Not your choice.
I realised love, family, responsibility,
it was all a sham.
Nothing was real.
Nothing was real?
And everything is real
with Kevin?
Tell me, Chandni!
- Does everything feel real with Kevin?
- You're disgusting, Aarav.
- Tell me...
- Just leave, Aarav!
Aarav, I'm sorry...
Aarav, I'm sorry.
I was acting on impulse.
The meds were at home.
You can take Kavya out.
But just be a bit more careful.
Thank you so much, Chandni.
Thank you.
Let me pass the test of love
Let me hold you in my arms
I have always yearned for you
There's a pooja for Kavya tomorrow.
Let me celebrate your love
Celebrate your love
Let me pass the test of love
My life belongs to you
I am yours
You are mine
My life belongs to you
I am yours
You are mine
I am very happy. Actually,
I'm relieved.
Kavya is very comfortable
with Aarav now.
And you?
- What do you mean?
- You know what I mean.
I still have feelings for Aarav.
But we can never be together.
And us?
Can we be together?
Kevin, you've stood by me
in my most difficult time,
and I really respect that.
I know.
It's... it's just too early
for me.
Well, I just wanted to put
my feelings out there.
Want to tell you
that I really like you.
As far as love is concerned,
if you respect me, I've enough love
for us both.
But no pressure.
Whatever you decide, I'll respect that.
You have given me more love
Than I deserve
I must have done many good deeds
To have won your love
I am indebted to you
A debt I must repay
Let me celebrate your love
Celebrate your love
Let me pass the test of love
Let me hold you in my arms
Hello.
Aarav, I've sent you the location pin.
Come soon.
Where?
Sis, why did you call me here?
Why didn't you tell me?
Just hear them out.
For my sake.
Just relax.
Aarav...
Aarav!
- Namaste!
- Aarav!
Namaste!
How are you?
Namaste, Aunty, I'm fine.
You look drawn.
Come with us to Udaipur. Okay?
Chandni, you come too.
A nice change of scenery.
We can spend time together,
and we'll get a chance to spend time
with Kavya too.
Mummy, what's going on?
What's going on?
We weren't there for your wedding, son.
So let's celebrate your first
anniversary together.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please put your hands together
for a very special couple
celebrating their very first wedding
anniversary.
Aarav and Chandni!
This one's for you!
To love, laughter and many more
anniversaries ahead!
Congratulations!
Aarav-Chandni, c'mon!
Get up! Be a sport.
Do it.
You're acting like you didn't
know about this.
Take the cake away.
Aarav!
We do know!
And that's why we're here.
You came here to prove
our marriage was a mistake.
You're here to mock us.
You're the ones making
a mockery of marriage.
The warranty on an LED bulb
is one year.
And you haven't managed that?
Kids today don't have an ounce
of patience.
They don't stick to anything,
so quick to move on.
No point explaining, Papa.
You've never understood me.
I have to know what's going on
in your life to understand you.
Ever talk to us?
Why bother talking to you
when you never listen?
All you care about is what people
will say.
One second, I...
One second.
This circus, this cake, these musicians,
it's all for your benefit,
not mine.
Aarav, mind your manners, please.
Okay. I'm listening.
Tell me.
What went so wrong in one year,
to want a divorce?
Chandni, my dear. You tell me.
You tell me.
What happened?
- Why are you doing all this, Mama?
- You're still very young.
You don't realise this is
a lifelong decision.
When we were getting married,
you warned us we were too young.
Now we're separating, you're using
the same logic!
My dear, if you're angry with Aarav,
tell me.
I'll fix him.
If he's made a mistake,
I apologise to you on his behalf.
Mummy, what are you doing?
Chandni, what's the problem?
You know we can help.
You can't help.
It's a compatibility issue.
For a relationship to last,
you need compatibility and compromise.
At least try.
Impossible, aunty. Sorry.
This is wrong.
You're hiding behind big words
like 'compatibility'!
Aarav, where are you going?
Let's go downstairs and talk,
if you won't talk in front
of the others.
We have to solve things.
Why else are we here?
- Definitely.
- Then what's the problem?
Mama, stop it! Leave it.
Tell us what the problem is.
Chandni, you must tell us.
- Neither of you are talking.
- It's my mistake, Mummy.
I raised a hand on Chandni.
Aarav!
What?
Chandni?
How dare you hit my daughter?
Aunty, sit down, please.
He apologised and admitted
he was wrong.
As if he's doing a big favour?
And you hid that from me.
From me?
Aarav, is this true?
Aarav, what happened?
It's true. He's admitted
he raised a hand on her.
Please sit down.
Let's understand what happened.
Vandana-ji, how dare he hit her?
This may be acceptable in your family,
but not in ours.
It's never happened before in our family.
And in your family? You shy away
from responsibility and run for it.
One small tiff and the divorce
papers follow. Who taught her that?
Mummy, calm down.
- What are you saying, Vandana-ji?
- It's the truth.
Mama, don't make matters worse.
What are you saying?
What's your son saying?
Let him talk.
Aarav, speak up!
We didn't come here to argue.
Aarav, if it's your mistake,
speak up.
Mama, please!
There's someone else in my life.
What!
We're very serious about each other.
We're getting married.
Who is he?
My colleague.
Kevin.
This love I feel for you
Has anyone ever loved like this before?
It is so rare
That such a lover is born
I bowed before God
So He would grant me your love
Happy anniversary, Chandni!
And congratulations!
Let the Lord above now
bless my decision
That I will love you forever
My heart is now all yours
Your love is like bright moonlight
The moon of my heart
A love that never fades
A love you can test
The moon of my heart
Hi!
Here.
I'm sorry, Aarav.
That wasn't the way to tell you.
I knew my world would end
when you left me,
but to expect you not to move on
would be selfish.
I understand why you want
to move on.
But what can I do?
It hurts so much.
I knew it would,
but not as much as this.
You really are moon-like.
A divine light,
arrogant
and distant.
My life belongs to you
I am yours
You are mine
My life belongs to you
I am yours
You are mine
Oh shit! I must have crushed
your backup cigarettes.
What did you used to say?
If I get stressed, I smoke
three ciggies, back-to-back.
Stress turns to smoke.
Calmness!
You smoked them already?
What do you think?
I don't know.
Quitting smoking was my gift
to you, Chandni.
I'll never take back.
Happy anniversary.
Happy anniversary, Aarav.
It's our last anniversary.
Want to celebrate?
Happy anniversary, Chand.
Happy anniversary, Aaru.
Kavya?
She's asleep. She waited for you
for hours.
No one looks as lovely to me as you
We're like those legendary lovers of old
I can see you with my eyes closed
Now my eyes no longer need dreams
This is it! This is really it!
The magic of you
Hi, Kevin. Yes.
I'm not home now.
See you soon.
Bye.
The love that I thought
so meaningful
Has torn my heart apart
Today the very name of love
Has changed to destruction
Aarav, I forgot my bag.
Bye.
It's not as though
I no longer love you
What can I do?
If I can no longer trust love
This is not the first time
That my heart has been broken
What can I do?
If I can no longer trust love
The love that I thought
so meaningful
Has torn my heart apart
Today the very name of love
Has changed to destruction
The love that I thought
so meaningful
Has torn my heart apart
Today the very name of love
Has changed to destruction
Item number 14.
Case number 236 of 2021,
Aarav Rawat vs. Chandni Prasad.
I was right
And so were you
Then why did our story
take the wrong turn?
Love made a decision for us
It had no right to make
when we were so young
Complaints were aplenty
But no one is to blame
What can I do?
If I can no longer trust love
The love that I thought
so meaningful
Has torn my heart apart
Today the very name of love
Has changed to destruction
I no longer trust love
Mama, pass me the turmeric.
- Have you cut the okra stems?
- Yes.
Hope it's not too much.
Mama, I'm happy with Kevin.
I feel safe with him.
Chandni, you're still carrying the traumas
of childhood.
You aren't running from love
but from that fear.
Mama, I don't want Kavya to have
a childhood like mine.
I want her to have a complete family.
To have both parents.
And I feel safe with Kevin.
I don't want to talk about this
anymore.
I feel safe with Kevin.
I feel safe...
Who can solve this?
Anu, come. Solve it for us.
Come on.
Come on, Anu.
Come on, Anu! I know you'll do
a good job.
Which job, sir?
Didn't I warn you last time?
What's wrong, sir? You look stressed.
Is the divorce through?
Brother, what road is this?
A shortcut, sir.
Sir, give me two minutes.
Hello, sir! Where are you off to?
Out!
Find the...
value of X.
Enough!
Run, run.
Come on, let's go.
Aarav.
I know you didn't like
some of the things we said.
We didn't appreciate some of
the things you said either.
We both believed we were right.
Son, maybe we didn't explain
things the right way.
But our intentions were good.
Do as you want.
But take care of yourself.
Stay well, stay healthy.
Your mother can at least
ask that of you.
I wanted to talk to you, Chandni.
I'm right outside.
What happened to your head?
I came to my senses!
You were right, Chandni.
You were always the smarter one.
I blamed you and Kavya
for my own failures.
I was wrong.
I just couldn't accept it.
That's why I took my frustration
out on you.
I saw your mother downstairs.
She reminded me
of the trust you had in me
when you left home.
I'm sorry I let you down.
I was a passable boyfriend,
but a terrible husband.
Honestly, I've never expected too much
from myself.
But I do want Kavya to be proud
of her father.
I want to try.
I'm going to the US for
my Masters.
For two years.
Papa will support me
for the first six months,
then I'll figure something out.
That's... that's great news, Aarav!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Okay then...
How many years will you be gone?
When do you leave?
For the US?
In about a week.
May I make one small request?
I know
it isn't fair for me to ask you
to stay in touch,
but if you break ties completely,
then Kavya will forget me,
like you will.
Please,
let's not become strangers.
Kavya won't forget you.
I won't let that happen, Aarav.
Thank you so much.
Oh God!
I tried to see you as a stranger
But that made me fall for you
all over again
I just hugged you.
I just hugged you back.
I kissed you on your forehead.
Let us be
Let us be strangers again
As though
We had never met
Let us be strangers again
Let us meet once again as strangers
And relive the past again
This time may our hearts
Tread the same paths
Hi, Paapu! How are you?
I miss you.
How's studies?
I miss you too, my sweetie.
Studies are good. How are you?
Is Mama okay?
It's time for class.
We'll talk again soon. Bye!
Let us make this promise to ourselves
Promises that we can keep
We may have some complaints
But may our love be greater
My broken heart tells me
Let us be strangers again
Let us be
Joining us on stage is a former,
never-to-be-forgotten student.
Our alumna, Chandni Prasad!
Please welcome her
with a special performance.
Lovely, Chandni!
Chandni! Chandni!
Wow, Chandni!
You set the stage on fire!
Aarav said you wouldn't show up.
If I'd told you, it wouldn't have
been a surprise.
Mama, you're so good!
Thank you, my baby.
It felt like a repeat telecast
of college days.
Chandni.
Kevin called. He had an urgent meeting,
so he couldn't come.
Where's Aarav?
I'm confused, sir.
Should I do an MS or an MBA?
My parents insist I do an MBA.
Do whatever you really want,
or you'll regret it later.
Chandni ma'am!
Ma'am, please come in.
Everything's changed so much.
But our painting is still here.
Ma'am, that's why most students
fight to have this room.
Wow! You both are twinning!
Our love story has become legendary.
Of course.
Legendary love stories
always have a tragic ending.
But I am.... I'm very happy
for you.
You did what you really wanted to.
What are your plans now?
I'll stay here.
Near Kavya.
Two years have gone by.
I don't want to miss any more
of her childhood.
Aarav,
that night...
when we fought,
I was broken.
Like someone had taken the wind
out of my sails.
And I had nothing left.
I still think of that night,
Chandni,
and I'm so embarrassed.
I'm really very...
You've said sorry enough times,
now listen to me.
Okay.
I felt so bad. I didn't want
to see your face again.
I signed the divorce papers
in anger.
I decided to marry Kevin.
Then, on the day of our engagement,
you came...
I felt it all slip away...
my anger, my stubbornness.
I wanted to stop you,
to say you'll always be a part
of Kavya's life,
but mine too.
From that moment until now,
not a single day has passed
without me missing you.
I used to long for the time
that you'd call Kavya.
So I could see you, hear you.
I'd feel happy and sad too.
How did I let you go?
Why didn't I stop you?
The sky could not tolerate
the pain of separation
The eyes of the moon filled with tears
Has it ever crossed your mind
That the sky too has lost its moon?
The drowning sky has returned
To hold the moon once more
For every wound, for every ache
The moon found healing
Why didn't you stop me?
If you had, I would've stayed.
I knew that. That's why I didn't
stop you.
It was important for you to go
to the US.
Finally you were getting your life
back on track.
I couldn't come in your way again.
I was in pain too, Aarav.
If only you had stopped me.
If you had, we could have been
together today, Chandni.
We'd be together now.
Why are you telling me
all this?
Why tell me now, when everything's over?
There's nothing between us now.
Why must you hurt me more?
I could have got by alone,
but hearing you say...
that you love me,
yet you can't be mine.
How can I live with that thought?
Go.
Go to Kevin.
I broke off the engagement with Kevin
the same day.
I told no one but Mama
and Jyotsna.
I went far away from you,
hoping that I could forget you.
I tried so hard
not to go on loving you.
- But I couldn't stop.
- Neither could I.
Not even for a second, Aaru.
Are you sure we're not making
another mistake?
It wasn't a mistake,
and if it was, so be it!
You have to be crazy
when you fall in love.
O moon of my heart
You are the star that brightens
the dark night
O moon of my heart
Paapu!
Hey, kiddo!
My baby! How's my sweetheart?
Your sweetheart missed you so much.
My sweetheart missed me so much?
How much?
This much.
Oh wow! This much!
And Mama missed Paapu how much?
This much only?
Come on, guys!
If the family reunion is done,
let's have a friends' reunion.
Come on! The sun's rising!
Hurry.
Let's go.
The power of love comes not in moments,
but in the long-run.
I am happy we met when we were 21.
Yes, we lacked maturity.
But perhaps the journey would not
have been the same,
and our love would not have become
as deep as it is.
I was given this life of mine
So I'd spend it wanting you
But one lifetime is not enough
To love you
O moon of my heart
You are the star that lights
the dark night
O moon of my heart
You are the star that lights
the dark night
O moon of my heart
A love that never fades
It's a love you can test
O moon of my heart
I was given this life of mine
So I'd spend it wanting you
But one lifetime is not enough
To love you
In this lifetime I promise you
That all my lifetimes will belong
to you
O moon of my heart
A love that never fades
It's a love you can test
O moon of my heart
The sky could not tolerate
the pain of separation
The eyes of the moon filled with tears
Has it ever crossed your mind
That the sky too has lost its moon?
The drowning sky has returned
To hold the moon once more
For every wound, for every ache
The moon found healing
My heart is now all yours
Your love is like bright moonlight
O moon of my heart
A love that never fades
It's a love you can test
O moon of my heart
No one looks as lovely
as you seem to me
We're like those legendary lovers of old
No one looks as lovely
as you seem to me
We're like those legendary lovers of old
I see you with my eyes closed
Now my eyes no longer
need to dream
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
I care far less for myself
Than I care about you
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
No one looks as lovely
as you seem to me
We're like those legendary lovers of old
No one looks as lovely
as you seem to me
We're like those legendary lovers
of old
Without you
What's life?
Through your eyes, when
I see myself
I look more beautiful
I have no need to adorn myself
Every day is a celebration
when you take me in your arms
It matters little if it's really
a day for celebration
Her velvety voice echoes in the air
Now my eyes no longer
need to dream
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
I care far less for myself
Than I care about you
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
That's really it,
that's really it
The magic of you
No one looks as lovely
as you seem to me
We're like those legendary lovers of old
No one looks as lovely
as you seem to me
We're like those legendary lovers of old
Without you
What's life?
You and me feel like one
How do I find the words...
to express my love?
I can belong to no one else.
Now that you are mine
How do I find the words...
to express my love?
I can belong to no one else.
Now that you are mine
You and me feel like one
Nothing else matters to me
but loving you
You know it's true -
youth is the time for love
How do I find the words...
to express my love?
I can belong to no one else.
Now that you are mine
Our story is on the lips
of the world
How love possesses us
How you and I
Care so little for the world